《生活大爆炸》前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory.
您好
Hello.
我来找霍华德·沃罗威茨
I'm looking for Howard Wolowitz.
我能问一下你找他有什么事吗
May I ask what this is about?
不能问
No, you may not.
是的官爷
Very well.
威廉姆斯上校  有什么需要我效劳的吗
Hi, Colonel Williams, how can I help you?
当然  周四见面没问题
Okay, sure, I can meet with you on Thursday.
约加州理工学院也没问题
Caltech is fine.
好  我能问问是什么事吗
Yeah, and may I ask what this is about?
不能啊
I may not?
他也是这么对我说的
That's what he said to me.
瞧瞧
Look at this.
埃隆·马斯克有个理论  我们每个人
Elon Musk has a theory that we're all just characters
都只是某高等文明的电玩游戏中的角色
in some advanced civilization's video game.
所以有某个外星小孩花钱
So some alien kid spent his money
来帮我升了气喘加近视眼的特性吗
on the asthma-and-glasses upgrade for me?
他没说是个好游戏啊
Well, he doesn't say it's a good game.
-咱们有麻烦了  -怎么了
- All right, we got a problem. - What's up?
空军对我们的量子陀螺仪有兴趣
The Air Force contacted me about our quantum gyroscope.
-他们想见面谈谈  -真的吗
- They want to have a meeting. - Really?
对啊  有个军队的人来到霍华德家找他
Yeah. This military guy showed up at Howard's door.
他可吓人了
He was terrifying.
他说什么了
Oh, what did he say?
他给了我他的名片
He gave me his business card
然后请我把名片转交给霍华德
and asked me to please pass it along to Howard.
这听起来不吓人啊
That doesn't sound terrifying.
土生土长的美国白人当然不觉得
To a white guy born here, no.
但如果你是棕色皮肤  名字带很多音节的话
If you are a brown guy whose name has a lot of syllables in it --
胆都吓破了好吗
terrifying.
你知道如果军方宣称我们的研究属于机密
You realize if the military declares our research classified,
他们可以直接把整个研究拿走吧
they can take the whole thing away from us.
如果真发生这种事
And if that happens,
我们就永远不能卖做商用了
we'll never be able to sell it commercially.
就跟这一大笔钱说再见了
There goes our big payday.
我还指望拿到这笔钱呢
I was counting on that money--
我的收入得跟我老婆持平
I need to make as much as my wife
这样我在床上才不用这么拼死拼活
so I don't have to try so hard in bed.
你也要这样吗
You do that, too?
当然  不然你觉得我怎么保持这么瘦的
Oh, yeah. How do you think I stay this thin?
先生们  我们都忽视了真正的问题
Gentlemen, I think we are losing sight of the real issue.
我们离成为军工业集合体中
We are on the precipice of becoming faceless cogs
无名无姓的小齿轮只有一步之遥了
in the military-industrial complex.
这难道不让人激动吗
Isn't that exciting?
你是在开玩笑吧
You're kidding, right?
才不是呢  像《星球大战》中那些风暴兵
Not at all. In Star Wars, when the stormtroopers
以完美的队形行军
would march in perfect formation,
前往骚扰民众时  你难道没有想过
harassing civilians, didn't you ever think,
"我也能成为这伟大军团的一员"吗
"Hey, that could be me"?
谢尔顿  我们可能成为
Sheldon, we could be contributing
未来几千年迫害人类的武器系统的
to a weapons system that oppresses mankind
幕后元凶呢
for the next thousand years.
好的  霍华德同意加入  你呢  莱纳德
Okay, Howard's on board. What do you think, Leonard?
我好担心霍华德啊
I'm worried about Howard.
打从军队的人来家里找他后
Ever since that guy from the Air Force showed up,
他就被吓到尿不停
he's been a nervous wreck.
我们在一个大型制药公司上班
All right, we work at a giant pharmaceutical company.
给他搞几片抗忧郁药吃吃啊
Get him some anti-anxiety meds.
他不愿意吃除了摩登原始人咀嚼维生素片
He won't take any pills that aren't chewable
以外的任何药物
and shaped like a Flintstone.
每当莱纳德感到焦虑的时候
You know, when Leonard's feeling anxious
我就让他散步久一点
I make him take a long walk.
这招有效吗
Does that help?
有效时间就一会儿  然后这烦人精就回来了
Well, for a while. Then he comes back.
-真是不敢相信  -怎么了
- I don't believe this. - What's wrong?
有个男同事发消息来恭喜我怀孕了
This guy from the office just congratulated me on being pregnant.
你本来知道自己怀了孕的  对吧
You did already know, right?
但是同事都不知道啊
No one at the office did.
-你有告诉任何人吗  -没有
- Did you tell anyone? - No.
你不让我跟别人说
You told me not to.
肯定是搞逆转录病毒的芭芭拉·陈传出去的
I bet it was Barbara Chen in retrovirus.
她貌似某天早上有听到我在孕吐
She might have heard me throwing up one morning.
自从她装助听器后  她就觉得自己可牛逼了
Every since she got the hearing aid, she thinks she's so great.
你为什么不想别人知道呢
Why don't you want anyone to know?
因为我有机会做一个免疫疗法研究的大项目
'Cause I'm up for a major immunotherapy study,
如果他们发现我怀孕了
and if they find out I'm pregnant
可能就会把机会给别人了
they might give it to someone else.
他们真的会这样吗
Would they really do that?
肯定会啊  去年芭芭拉就是这么被换掉
I know they would-- they did it to Barbara Chen last year
因为我爆料说她怀孕了
when I told everyone she was pregnant.
我要发条朋友圈  说我的好朋友们
Wait till I Snapchat that my friends might be working
为政府的机密项目做事
on a top secret government project.
你是不是疯了
Are you crazy?
你怎么能把这事写到朋友圈
You can't put that on Snapchat.
好吧  那我写到过时几百万年的脸书上吧
Fine, I'll put it on Facebook like a caveman.
或许应该在会面前  找个律师谈谈
You know, maybe before our meeting we should talk to a lawyer.
这主意不差
That's not a bad idea.
你家族里肯定有人是律师吧
Well, you must have someone in your family that's a lawyer.
为啥  就因为我是犹太人吗
Why? Because I'm Jewish?
这就跟我说  "你是印度人
That's like me saying, "Hey, you're Indian.
你肯定有亲戚在电话客服中心工作吧"
Doesn't your cousin work in a call center?"
我还真有亲戚在电话客服中心工作
My cousin does work in a call center.
我也真有亲戚是律师
And my cousin's a lawyer.
我们不需要霍华德的亲戚帮忙
We don't need Howard's cousin, no.
咱们有我啊
We have me.
谢尔顿  你不是律师  你只是爱耍聪明
You're not a lawyer, Sheldon, you're just a know-it-all.
我才不是耍聪明
I am not a know-it-all.
我只是个上知天文下知地理
I'm a person who knows lots of things
还喜欢在别人犯错时  热心纠正他们的人
and likes to correct other people when they're wrong.
这就是所谓爱耍聪明的人啊
That's the definition of being a know-it-all.
或是德文里的"砖家"
Or in German, a Besserwisser.
你怎么能觉得你能瞒住你怀孕的事实
How did you think you were gonna hide your pregnancy?
我有整套计划  我一直有四处留下巧克力棒包装
I had a plan-- I kept leaving Dove Bar wrappers around
来解释我为什么发福了
to explain any weight gain.
那你是上哪去弄的空巧克力棒包装纸
Where did you get empty Dove Bar wrappers?
当然是我吃完故意留的包装啊  老娘怀孕了
From all the Dove Bars I ate! I'm pregnant!
用点脑想想好吗
Try to keep up!
抱歉  我得去看看我老板发现没
I'm sorry. I-I have to go find out if my boss knows.
无论如何  我们都会支持你
Well, whatever happens, we're here for you.
谢谢  你们最好了
Thanks. You guys are the best.
开车小心  我们爱你  到了打电话...
Yeah, drive safe. We love you. And give us a call...
要死了  是我  是我传的
Oh, my God, it was me, it was me!
是我大嘴巴告诉别人她怀孕的
I'm the one who blabbed she was pregnant!
-什么  -我不是故意的
- What?! - I didn't mean to.
就有天不小心跟她的助手说溜嘴了
It just slipped out in front of her assistant one day.
忘了拿外套
I... I forgot my coat.
来  亲爱的  外套拿去
Oh! Here's your coat, honey.
这外套太萌了
That's such a cute jacket.
天啊  我好内疚  我又骗了她
God, I feel so bad-- I just lied to her.
但你演技入木三分
Oh, but you did it so well.
真是太厉害了
That's amazing!
感觉像在看一个雕塑大师
It's like watching a sculptor,
但你用的材料是谎言
but your clay was lies.
现在的重点难道该是挖苦我吗
Is that really what's important right now?
我是说认真的  你得让我扫描你大脑
I mean, seriously, you have got to let me scan your brain
看看你撒谎时哪些区域会亮起
when you're being dishonest so I can see what lights up.
你这席话我受益良多
That's super helpful, Amy.
谢谢你全家啊  真想立刻让你扫描
Thanks a lot. I can't wait to do that.
我从这里就能看到一团臭三八细胞亮起
I can see a clump of bitch cells lightin' up from here.
等我一会  我打给我律师亲戚
Give me a second to call my cousin.
我想不出远在佛州劳德代尔堡的税务律师
I don't see how a tax lawyer from Fort Lauderdale
怎么能对知识财产权方面提出有用建议
could be helpful regarding intellectual property.
首先  他是在佛州的博卡拉顿
First of all, he's in Boca Raton,
那里比劳德代尔堡上档次多了
which is better than Fort Lauderdale.
更重要的是
But more importantly,
他上益智游戏节目撑了两天没被淘汰
he lasted two days on Jeopardy,
很明显他就是个聪明人
so he's clearly a smart guy.
你好
Hello.
马蒂  谢谢你愿意跟我们聊啊
Hey, Marty. Thanks for talking to us.
小事一桩
Hey, no problem.
真是"感谢"你上了太空  这下无论我干啥
Thanks for going to outer space so no matter what I do
我妈都会对我感到失望
my mom will be disappointed in me.
但我没娶信犹太教的老婆  也算扯平了
Well, I married a little Catholic girl, so we're even.
这位是莱纳德  这位是谢尔顿
Anyway, this is Leonard and Sheldon.
我们三个一起想出了这个导向系统
The three of us came up with the guidance system.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hello.
而这位是我的朋友拉杰
And this is my friend, Raj.
专利跟我无关  我在这里
Oh, I'm not on the patent. I'm just here
是因为我办公室里有只大黄蜂
because there's a bumblebee in my office.
我有看到  真的很大只
I saw it. It's big.
总之呢  如同我电邮里所说
Anyway, like I said in the e-mail,
见面定在这周四
this meeting's on Thursday.
你有什么建议可以给我们吗
Do you have any advice for us?
我对专利法了解不多
Well, I don't know much about patent law.
但我的建议是
But, uh, my advice is:
听听他们怎么说  有关信息尽量少说
hear them out, offer as little information as possible,
无论如何  绝对别签任何东西
and whatever you do, don't sign anything.
"别签任何东西"  这就是你的建议吗
"Don't sign anything"? That's your advice?
好吧  所以如果在会面中
Okay, so, uh, if during this meeting,
我们其中一个人画了一幅油画之类的
one of us were to, say, complete an oil painting,
你是在建议我们不要在上面签上名吗
you'd recommend that we leave that unsigned?
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
你话就是这么说的
That's what you said.
但我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
你就在博卡拉顿这么当律师的吗
This must be how you practice law in Boca Raton,
说着词不达意
by saying things you don't mean
言不由衷的话
and meaning things you don't say.
霍华德  他为啥要对我嚷嚷
Howard, why is he yelling at me?
好吧  你上过益智节目
All right, you were on Jeopardy.
让我学学主持人
Allow me to Alex Trebek
并把这件事用节目上的问题形式表达
this and put it in the form of a question:
在座是哪个垃圾  在浪费我们的时间呢
Who has been a complete waste of our time?
马蒂  晚点打给你
Marty, let me call you back.
某天我因为谋杀"某人"被控诉时
Someday, when I'm up on murder charges,
我会打给你
you'll be hearing from me.
不用找他  我来当你律师
You don't need him. I'll represent you.
-我来啦  -你怎么来了
- Hi. - Hey. What brings you by?
去参加我们新款安眠药的销售研讨会了
Oh, had to go to a sales seminar on our new sleeping pill.
-研讨会如何  -很棒啊
- Oh. How was it? - Great.
-睡着了吗  -开场两分钟就睡着了吧
- Fell asleep? - In, like, two minutes. Yeah.
一切情况还好吗
So, how is everything going around here?
还在为大家发现你怀孕这事不开心吗
Are you still upset about people finding out you're pregnant?
我真要气炸了
I'm furious.
当然  肯定的
Sure, sure.
你查清楚是谁说出去的吗
Uh, did you ever figure out who told?
没  我去找芭芭拉·陈对质了  但她说
No. I confronted Barbara Chen, but she claimed
她完全不知道我在说什么
she didn't know what I was talking about.
看来这事只能是未知的谜团了
Well, I guess it's just gonna remain a mystery,
就像研讨会把灯调暗后发生的事
you know, like whatever happened in that seminar
对我也是未知的谜团
after they dimmed the lights.
绝对是芭芭拉
It had to be Barbara.
我刚就一直在想办法报复她
I've been trying to figure out a way to get back at her.
你觉得用她工作用的电脑上网搜
Do you think using her work computer to Google
"怎么下海当鸡"会太过分吗
"How to be a prostitute" is over the line?
其实呢  在我高中的时候
Uh, you know, when I was in high school,
有个姑娘在我背后说我坏话
there was this girl who was talking about me behind my back,
所以我跟我朋友们
so me and all my friends,
把她围在厕所的角落  然后原谅了她
we cornered her in the bathroom and forgave her.
这算哪门子的报仇啊
What kind of revenge is that?
这臭娘们破坏我工作  我得整死她
This woman screwed with my job. She's got to pay.
好吧  亲爱的  其实呢
Okay, all right, honey, you know what?
我有一件昨天没胆跟你说的事
There was something I was too scared to tell you yesterday,
而现在我还是怕得要死不敢告诉你  其实...
a-and now... I'm just balls-out terrified to tell you, but...
真相是...
the truth is it...
大嘴巴的不是芭芭拉  是我
wasn't Barbara Chen, it was me.
是我让大家都知道的
I'm the reason everyone knows.
你为什么要这么做
Why did you do that?
不小心说漏嘴嘛  很抱歉我撒谎了
Well, it was an accident. I am so sorry I lied.
出去
Get out.
对了  厕所女同学的事我也撒谎了
Oh, you know, I also lied about the girl in the bathroom.
是的  我们其实把她的牙套保持器扔进了马桶
Yeah, we actually dumped her retainer in the toilet
然后又塞回她的嘴里
and put it back in her mouth.
我不懂为什么会面时我不能说话
I don't understand why I can't talk at this meeting.
因为你一开口就会激怒别人
'Cause when you talk, it enrages people.
好吧
Okay.
快问快答
Quick question.
我能跟这位上校
Am I allowed to exchange pleasantries
在会上寒暄一下吗
upon meeting this colonel?
准了
Yes.
那我能告诉他
Am I allowed to inform him
桑德斯上校并不是真正军队出身的吗
that Colonel Sanders was never actually in the military?
你正在激怒我
I'm getting enraged.
好吧
Fine.
我能用文字转语音软件吗
Can I use text-to-speech software?
-不行  -就不要说话
- No! - Don't speak.
啊  哇靠
Aw, nuts.
男士们
Gentlemen!
我是威廉姆斯上校
I'm Colonel Williams.
感谢抽空与我见面
Thank you for meeting with me.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hello.
你们中的哪一位是这个项目的主要设计者
So, which one of you is the brains behind all this?
这是大家共同努力的结果
It's a group effort,
但如果非得选一个主力  那应该是我吧
but I guess if we had to pick a main brain, it would be me.
因为量子涡旋
And because of the quantum vortices,
这玩意就具有永动性吗
this can run perpetually?
完全正确
Exactly.
看来你很懂物理嘛
Yeah, you have a good grasp of the physics.
-我是被培训出来的科学家  -是吗
- Well, I'm a scientist by training. - Really?
你是物理学家吗
You're a physicist?
比那强  我是工程师
Better. I'm an engineer.
你是哪里毕业的
Where did you go to school?
麻省理工
MIT.
真巧  我也是
Oh. Well, hey, me, too.
我早该知道
I should have known.
每一项伟大的发明背后都有我们校友的智慧结晶
Behind every great invention is an MIT mind.
我就不兜圈子了
I'll cut to the chase.
美国空军想将这项技术投入到实际应用中
The Air Force believes there's an application for this technology,
我们有兴趣投资你们的研究
and we're interested in funding your research.
多谢赏识  但你要知道
Well, thanks, but you should know
我们有点担心这项技术会被用到武器上
we're a little concerned about this being used in weapons.
这样啊  让我来放宽你心
Oh, well, let me put your mind at ease.
我们拿来干什么关你们屁事
What we use it for is none of your business.
我不知道该对此作何感想
I don't know how I feel about this.
伙计们  这只是一个导向系统
Look, guys, it's just a guidance system.
别想得好像你们交给我们的是
It's not like you're handing us
《星际迷航》的终极武器死星
the Death Star from Star Trek.
你们唯一需要顾虑的是
All you need to worry about is,
现在它这么大
right now, it's this big,
我们需要它变得...这么点大
and we need it to be... this big.
那要大大减小很多啊
That's a lot less big.
没错  减小的程度有这么大
Yes, it's... this much less big.
我都不确定可不可行
I'm not even sure that's possible.
我问过几个麻省理工的同事
Well, I ran it by some colleagues at MIT,
他们认为四个月就能搞定
and they thought they could get it done in four months.
-四个月  -那我们两个月就能搞定
- Four months? - Yeah, we'll do it in two!
你好  我是谢尔顿·库珀博士
Hi. I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
我才是这个项目的主力设计者
I'm the actual brains behind this project.
还有工程师不是真正的科学家
Also, engineers aren't real scientists,
麻省理工是一所职业学院
MIT's a trade school,
还有还有  死星来自《星球大战》不是《星际迷航》
and the Death Star is from Star Wars, not Star Trek!
撇开那些不说
But otherwise,
感谢为国服役
thank you for your service.
霍华德跟我说你要加班  所以我带了吃的来
Howard told me you were working late, so I brought dinner.
谢谢  我只是想安静地工作
Oh, thanks. You know, I just wanted to get some work done
不用每五分钟就有人跑来恭喜我怀孕了
without people congratulating me about the baby every five minutes.
我今天自己在实验室
I spent my day alone in the lab
陪一只炭疽感染的老鼠等死
waiting for a rat to die of anthrax.
你是来给我送吃的  还是来幸灾乐祸
Did you come here to bring me dinner or to gloat?
我是来看看你心情好点没
Well, I came to see how you were feeling,
但我猜还在生气呢
but I'm guessing still angry?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我老板要见我  我现在压力山大
My boss wants to meet with me, and I'm stressing.
你真的认为他们会开始区别对待你吗
You really think they're gonna start treating you differently?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我向来都被人区别对待
I've always been treated differently!
瞧我小体型  听我的小尖嗓
Look at me! Listen to me!
你看见我脑子里永远不会首先想到
I mean, the first thought when you see me isn't,
"那是一位科学家"
"That's a scientist."
你只会想"希望她不要跟妈妈走丢"
It's, "I wonder if her mommy knows where she is."
我好后悔给你买了欢乐儿童餐
I am really regretting that I got you a Happy Meal.
我那么努力工作才坐上这个位置
I've worked so hard to get where I am,
我不想因为怀孕
and I don't want to get sent back to square one
就被打回原点
because I'm pregnant.
我懂你的感受
I understand how you feel.
谢谢
Thank you.
真希望我能做些什么让你好过点
I wish there were some way I could make it better.
你给我买了薯条  这是好的第一步
Well, you brought me French fries. That's a start.
其实我给你买了切片苹果  因为你怀孕了嘛
Uh, actually, I got you apple slices 'cause you're pregnant.
切片苹果
Apple slices?
哪个傻逼会去麦当劳买水果啊
What kind of lunatic goes to McDonald's and gets fruit?!
小的立马重新买
I'll be right back.
老娘还要巧克力奶昔
And a chocolate shake!
你做什么呢
What are you doing?
莱纳德生我气了  我给他做柠檬方块呢
Oh, Leonard's mad at me, so I'm making him lemon bars.
他爱吃柠檬方块吗
Does he even like lemon bars?
不爱吃
Not really.
但我也在生他的气  所以就柠檬方块吧
But I'm mad at him, too, so lemon bars it is.
会面时发生什么事了吗
Something happen at the meeting?
他们逼我保证不说话
They made me promise I wouldn't talk.
-结果你说话了  -你看吧
- And you talked? - Well, now, see?
你都知道会发生什么事了
You knew what was gonna happen.
他们怎么就不知道呢
Why didn't they?
总之现在我们承诺了要在极短的时间内
Anyway, now we're committed to completing this project
完成这个项目
in a ridiculously short time frame,
大家都生我气了
and everyone's upset with me.
也许这能让你好过点
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
伯纳黛特也在生我的气
Bernadette's mad at me, too.
也许这能让你好过点
If it makes you feel any better,
有一种类型的寄生蜂
a parasitoid wasp known as Oobius depressus
在被认定灭绝101年后重新被发现踪迹了
has been rediscovered after 101 years of presumed extinction.
这怎么让我好过了
Why would that make me feel better?
那你跟伯纳黛特的事又怎么会让我好过
Why would your Bernadette thing make me feel better?
至少我的还有教育意义
At least mine was educational.
好吧  当我没说
Okay. Never mind.
对不起
Look, I'm sorry.
告诉我伯纳黛特为什么生你的气了
Tell me why Bernadette is upset with you.
我跟公司的人说了她怀孕的事
Well, I told people at work that she's pregnant.
但她没准备让他们知道
She wasn't ready for them to know.
你为什么要这么做
Why would you do that?
我就是说溜嘴了  我也很懊悔
Well, it just slipped out. I feel terrible.
跟我简直一模一样
See, that's exactly what happened to me,
除了我是故意说的  而且并不后悔
except that I said it on purpose, and I have no regrets.
两个月内完成有可能吗
Is it even possible to get this done in two months?
也许吧  不知道
Well, maybe. I don't know.
我们得每周不歇地一天工作12小时
We'll have to work 12 hours a day, seven days a week.
也就是说我不能再每天给佩妮做早餐了
Which means I won't be able to make Penny breakfast every day,
她会意识我做的法式吐司奶油卷
and she'll realize my brioche French toast
是唯一让她不跟我离婚的原因
was the only thing keeping her in the marriage.
我也爱吃你做的法式吐司
I love your French toast.
谢了  兄弟
Oh, thanks, man.
那你们为什么同意那个截止日期
So, why did you guys even agree to the deadline?
我们没同意  谢尔顿干的
We didn't. Sheldon did.
你就让他答应了
And you just let him?
上校还说这是苟利国家的事
Well, the colonel said it was for the good of the country,
我们就因资金而趋之了
and the funding is substantial.
没有  主要当时有一阵尴尬的沉默
No, but mostly, there was an awkward pause,
于是为了打破尴尬局面  我就说了"好"
and I broke it by saying, "Okay."
看来我要见不到你们一阵子了
So I guess I won't be seeing you guys for a while.
是这样的
Oh, looks like it. Wow.
你们去军方工作  独留我一人
You're going off to work with the military, leaving me behind.
我突然理解军嫂的生活了
Now I know how all those army wives feel.
你够了啊
Would you stop?
我们就是在大学另一端而已
We're just gonna be on the other side of campus.
也在这里
And right here.
你就是一傻姑娘
You are a deeply silly man.
他怎么如此不敢直面内心呢
He is so afraid of his feelings.
有空吗
Got a minute?
有啊  进来
Yeah, come on in.
我想道歉
I just wanted to apologize.
我知道你是不小心说出去的
I know what you did was an accident.
谢谢你  对不起  我跟你撒谎了
Oh, thank you, and I'm sorry I lied about it.
不过  你撒谎挺在行的
For what it's worth, you're a great liar.
艾米也这么夸我的
Oh, that's what Amy said.
研究项目怎么样了
So what's going on with the research project?
他们还会让你负责吗
Are they gonna let you run it?
老板说他还没定下来
Well, my boss said he hadn't decided yet,
于是我温柔地提醒了他
so I gently reminded him
他是个有钱白人老头
that he's an old rich white guy,
而我是个甜美无害的小孕妇
and I'm a sweet little pregnant lady
在陪审团面前演落泪戏码  没在怕的
who's not afraid to cry in front of a jury.
你威胁要告他
You threatened to sue?
我多年前就已学会  当你只有一米五
Hey, I learned a long time ago, when you're four feet eleven
而平视只能看到每个男人裆部时
and eye level with every guy's crotch,
你就往那里捶就对了
that's where you punch.
有点意思
That's funny.
我学到的不是捶  是...
I learned something totally different.
其实呢
Do you know what?
不过是个研究项目
It's just a research project.
世上最重要的工作
The most important job in the world
应该是抚养这个孩子
is gonna be raising this child.
那才赋予我生命的意义
It's all I need to give my life meaning.
说得太好了
Oh, that's so beautiful.
你信了  那就好
You believe me? Oh, good.
再多11个像你这样的笨蛋
11 more chumps like you,
整团陪审团就随老娘摆布了
I'll have the jury eating out of my hand.
我之前都不知道这栋楼是机密建筑
I never realized this building was classified.
也许正是因为它是机密
Maybe that's because it's classified.
希望不会离我们的车位太远
Wish we weren't so far from my parking space.
就你吃柠檬方块的那个熊样
The way you put away those lemon bars,
远点是好事
perhaps that's a good thing.
我希望恢复"你不许说话"规则
I'd like to reinstate the you-not-talking rule.
为什么  明显没用
Why? It clearly doesn't work.
危险
不得吸烟
应该就是这了
I guess this is it.
那是视网膜扫描仪吗
Is that a retinal scanner?
我们试试
Let's find out.
霍华德·沃罗威茨  准许入内
Howard Wolowitz-- access granted.
-不是吧  -太棒了
- No way! - Impressive!
该我了  该我了
Oh, my turn! My turn!
莱纳德·霍夫斯塔特  准许入内
Leonard Hofstadter-- access granted.
我都不需要把眼睛摘下来呢
I didn't even have to take my glasses off!
拒绝入内
Access denied.
它知道呢
It knows!
你们  大头朝下抱着我
Oh, oh, oh, oh, guys, hold me upside down!
霍华德·沃罗威茨  准许入内
Howard Wolowitz, access granted.